What is the most important part
about taking risks to be successful?
And are there any risks maybe outside of finance that you
had to take in order to get to where you are today?
Yeah, so to me, risk, there's lots
of different ways to think about risk.
But what I do with the companies that I'm
working in today, where I have my previous employers,
is it a risk that I can mitigate or fix?
If it's a risk way out of
my control, then it's out of your control.
You don't just take a flyer and
say, I can't control six of these variables.
I can only control two
and think that's a good idea.
If there's three variables that are risky and
you think you can control two of them,
then generally you have a pretty good shot.
But I just do believe
that everyone has a risk tolerance.
And I mean, Elon Musk, when
he invested so much money in Tesla,
he took basically all he made at PayPal,
threw it into another deal, and it hit huge.
He could have just put a little bit
in, and then he wouldn't be worth $250 billion.